<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chemical Sciences Society</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chemical Sciences Society</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chemistry Freshmen Orientation Camp</title>
      <link>/events/chemistryfoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/chemistryfoc/</guid>
      <description>One of the main events organized by CSS, Chemistry Freshmen Orientation Camp (FOC) is a 3D2N overnight camp targeted at Chemistry freshmen. Filled with fun bonding activities, Chemistry FOC will allow you to meet new friends that will accompany you through your university journey! It is also an opportunity to learn more about the Chemistry curriculum from your friendly seniors. Kickstart your university life with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>P and VPs</title>
      <link>/structure/pandvps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/pandvps/</guid>
      <description>The President and Vice Presidents are responsible for leading the normal operations of the committee. They oversee respective departments to ensure that activities and events were planned and executed in a timely manner. They chair meetings and make critical decisions to ensure that the goals of the management committee are achieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admin</title>
      <link>/structure/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/admin/</guid>
      <description>We are the people behind the scenes, who meticulously take care of various details, quantities and communications! We believe in running efficiently to help all other departments keep up with their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chemistry Night</title>
      <link>/events/chemnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/chemnight/</guid>
      <description>Chemistry Night is also one of the main annual events organized and it brings the NUS Chemistry family together for one final time at the end of each academic year. It bonds the Chemistry community together with delicious food, amazing games and exciting performances!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publicity</title>
      <link>/structure/publicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/publicity/</guid>
      <description>Want to find out more about the events organised by CSS? Check out all the posters designed and follow us on our social media accounts - these are all managed by Publicity! We are the team behind design and creativity and we aim to reach out to all the chemistry students and to keep everyone updated!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BASF Kids’ Lab</title>
      <link>/events/basf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/basf/</guid>
      <description>Volunteering at BASF Kids’ Lab by BASF Kids’ Lab Asia Pacific is a yearly initiative we undertake, where we do fun and simple science experiments with children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare</title>
      <link>/structure/welfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/welfare/</guid>
      <description>HEYY! Our marvelous welfare committee consists of 9 CARING and PASSIONATE members who aims to make your time in NUS chemistry an enjoyable one!! Year 1s GET READY, your welfare tea/dinner will be coming soon! Together as a committee, we will pack all chemistry students at least 1 welfare pack every AY! Email us on what you guys would like to see in your welfare pack and maybe it would magically appear in this AY’s pack :^)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essentials for Y1s</title>
      <link>/events/essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/essentials/</guid>
      <description>Essentials For Year 1 Chemistry helps kickstart the undergraduate life of Chemistry freshmen, and is held at the start of each academic year. Chemistry seniors will be present to share about their student experiences and curriculum planning so that freshmen are aware of the experiences and are able to plan ahead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>/structure/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/marketing/</guid>
      <description>Marketing: the people who find you these cool prizes behind our giveaways, and the good stuff in your welfare packs!! :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Researchers</title>
      <link>/events/researchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/researchers/</guid>
      <description>Meet the Researchers is an annual event that connects NUS faculty and researchers with students, allowing students to find out more about ongoing research projects in the department. Curious about Undergraduate Research Opportunities Program in Science (UROPS) and Final Year Project (FYP) opportunities available in NUS? This is definitely an event you would not want to miss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/structure/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structure/projects/</guid>
      <description>We are the main people in charge of the various events you see in our events calendar! Join us in having fun from preparing games for orientation to creating a meaningful farewell during Chemistry Night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare Tea</title>
      <link>/events/welfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/welfare/</guid>
      <description>CSS also organizes occasional welfare teas for the Chemistry freshmen when it is nearing recess week/reading week! What is better than food when it comes to motivation for exams?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history/</guid>
      <description> About Heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> Join us in our journey CSS is always looking for eager students to help us in our work. From corporate liaising to organising orientations to publishing websites, we require a wide repertoire of talents for our diverse events. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, do check out our annual events calendar below, and feel free to go to our contact page to get in touch with us!
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>